question_data = [

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Studies suggest that approximately 40% of the world population is left-handed.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The disease cancer in itself is not contagious.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Pluto is a planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"March 10th is also known as Mar10 Day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}

]

#data from https://opentdb.com/api_config.php